Ms. Huo.
I have reliable news.
Mr. Meng is a Japanese spy.
Don't believe him.
Deyou.
No.
He's a spy.
We need evidence.
Where is the evidence?
Spy? Where is the evidence?
Long Yue.
Don't listen to him.
Speaking of spies,
he's the spy, Deyou.
Brother, trust me.
Rumor has it that
the son-in-law of Shangguan Bao.
For the position of Shangguan Bao,
for Shangguan Bao’s position.
All right, Zhi Dong.
Shut up!
Stop it.
Twelve.
Let me tell you.
My valley
is the furnace of Supreme Lord Lao.
can tolerate all kinds of demons.
As long as we are here,
we have to practice it.
I want to see
whether you can make a monkey
or a Bone Spirit?
Long Yue.
Don't move.
I...
It hurts.
It's just a minor injury.
Zhi Ling.
Long Yue.
Did you hurt yourself in Luoyang that day?
You have good eyesight.
It wasn't left that day.
It was left yesterday.
Be gentle.
Who's your brother?
You keep telling the truth.
All right.
You...
It hurts.
There's no one else now.
To be honest,
How did you get hurt?
Brother, I...
I was beaten up by someone.
Look at you.
I...
Brother.
I came back
I came back to inform you.
Long Yue.
Do you know?
The rule of Qinglong Camp
should be Shangguan Bao’s daughter.
Shangguan Ying inherited the position of Patriarch
was occupied by He Xiaopian.
Now Shangguan Ying is missing.
I heard
he was killed by He Xiaopian.
Brother, He Xiaopian is so vicious.
Do you know why
Do you know why?
It's because
in Qinglong Hideout.
Why do I hear something from you?
No, brother, no.
Think about it.
How could He Xiaopian
take over the position of Patriarch?
While his foundation is unstable,
take our men
to take back Qinglong Hideout.
Among these three axes,
except Shangguan Bao,
is you, Ms. Huo.
Long Yue.
must be you.
Like a brother,
Yes.
Anyway,
I have a great news
waiting for you.
What is it? Tell me.
Brother.
Cai Yun is the murderer who killed Shangguan Bao.
Hand him over.
All the men of Qinglong Fortress
listen to you?
If you become the Patriarch,
the Golden Treasure
is yours, right?
That makes sense.
You have a foresight.
He left me
for me.
Really?
Congratulations.
Brother
What does the treasure map look like?
Show it to me.
Let me tell you.
Ask what you should.
Don't ask what you shouldn't.
Yes, listen to me.
Long Yue.
I always see you holding this knife.
Does this knife
to you?
The scabbard
left it to me.
She left it to me.
Ni still doesn't eat?
A little.
I spit it out.
Long Yue.
Here's to you, Second Brother.
Long Yue, it's better to stay in QinFo Ye Ravine.
Let's drink then.
Brother.
Come on, brother.
From now on,
you'll be the head of the 18 strokes.
Here's to you.
Great!
Here's to you, brother.
Cheers.
Brother.
Deyou.
Deyou!
No!
Mother! Father!
No! No!
It's okay, Ni. Don't be afraid.
No.
There's no doctor in QinFo Ye Ravine.
If this continues,
Can Ni hold on?
If the herbs don't work,
we have to take her down the mountain.
She has been through this hardship at such a young age.
It's really hard for her.
The war is in chaos.
Humans are like ants.
Everyone has to bear
in their destiny.
What?
You don't know me?
I'm impressed.
Last night, I thought about
in the Three Duods.
People
grow up
through setbacks.
You are...
I am...
Eagle is...
Ni will be the same.
Like a big tree.
Only through wind and rain
the roots can implant the land deeply.
and stand steadily.
So,
we don't have to worry too much.
We need to worry about the Meng Shi rule.
Did you see the Meng Shi rule?
No, why?
Oh no.
He got away by accident.
and stole Long Yue's scabbard.
Who ran away?
There's nothing in the sheath.
Tahara-san, look!
A poem.
The sky in the northwest is lowering and the sky is high.
Wide pine sea dew hawk
Linglu.
Linglu Peak
You mean
the treasure might be here.
It's very likely.
According to the Meng Shi rule,
Your Majesty.
Let me ask you.
Is there a place called Ling Qiu Peak in Shaanxi?
Linglu Peak?
With this mountain,
It's in the northwest direction of Shaanxi.
Okay.
Take us to Linglu Peak tomorrow.
OK.
Stop.
How far is Linglu Peak?
Great Lord, did you see it?
That mountain is...
Speed up!
Hide!
Someone ambushed us.
Deyou. Deyou.
What's wrong?
The Meng Shi rule wants to run. I'll go after him.
Let him go.
According to the Meng Shi rule, he forgot something from his ancestors.
I'll deal with him later.
We're mainly dealing with Tian Yuan.
Luckily, I was on guard against him.
Keep it well.
Without this third picture,
even if they have the first two,
it's useless.
Brother, bad news!
We're surrounded.
Hang in there!
Huo Lang.
You're surrounded by me.
Why don't we stop the war
and talk about it?
I have nothing to talk with the Japanese.
I respect you for being a man.
If you surrender,
and hand over the real treasure map,
I'll let your brothers go.
Didn't you get the treasure map?
The treasure map many years ago.
The sheep skin smells fishy.
You can fool
You can fool the Meng Shi rule,
but not me.
You're not stupid.
I didn't fool you.
Huo Lang.
I won't argue with you.
As long as you hand over the treasure map,
and share the gold
Let's share it, okay?
Nonsense!
The gold belongs to us Chinese.
Dream on!
Guys, beat him up!
No.
Why didn't I find Cai?
Brother.
Look who's here.
Wen Pei, I never thought
to kill demons with you on the battlefield.
We are together again like when we were young.
It feels good.
The reinforcements are here.
Miss Cai's trap is set up.
A trap?
What trap?
Do you think the sheep skin in the buns
can fool him?
No, what should we do?
How about this?
Let's split up into three groups.
along the way,
to ambush near Linglu Peak.
and ambush Tachihara.
Second, I'll go find Cui Wenkui.
Bring his soldiers here.
In this way, if Tian Yuan plottes,
we won't be afraid.
Okay.
The third road.
Liu half catty and Bao went to Qinglong Fortress to save Shangguan Eagle
to Qinglong Fortress to save Shangguan Ying.
Miss Cai, you're so smart.
You are Zhuge Liang.
Cai Zhuge, you can stay here.
and be our advisor.
Ms. Huo.
We're not in the same field.
But I respect you as a hero.
What did you say?
You said I'm a hero.
Do you really think so?
Guys, our reinforcements are here.
Beat them hard!
Brothers, fight!
Charge!
This way.
Young Master, here.
Follow me.
Hide. I'll do it.
Bastard!
Where is the gun?
In front.
Let's take a look.
Miss Cai.
You came just in time.
The devil almost made dumplings.
Ms. Huo, good for you.
Guys,
Today, I'll chop off Zheng Xiong Tahara's head!
Charge!
Yes!
Brothers, go!
Lie down.
Get down.
Hurry up.
Eagle.
After him!
Are you okay?
Let's go.
Retreat! Retreat!
Deyou!
Twelve.
Long Yue.
I can't play with you anymore.
Wang Shi Er!
Wang Shi Er, you can't die!
Ms. Huo, go!
Zheng Xiong Tian Yuan, I have to kill him.
The enemy's firepower is too strong.
Masao Tahara!
I have to kill him. Let's go.
Take him away!
No, I have to kill Masao Tachihara.
Go!
Come up.
Come on.
Here.
Eagle.
Lord Tanihara!
I didn't expect you to come so fast.
I received your help.
A team has arrived.
Good.
There's another good news.
What?
The main force has arrived in Shanzhou.
Good.
Great!
God is on my side.
God is on our side.
I'm sorry
I've made you suffer.
Eagle.
I'm sorry to Madam.
and you.
I made you suffer.
I'm the one who should apologize.
I misunderstood you
and shot you.
It's my fault.
I'm fine.
It's all done.
Don’t worry about it.
I can figure out how Madam died.
I didn’t get shot in vain.
I don't understand.
A person who watched me grow up.
who I trust the most.
He lied to me
and killed my father.
and Meixiang’s aunt.
Why did Uncle He become like this?
Everything will pass.
Yes.
Where is Liu?
Mr. Liu carried you here.
He went back to Qinglong Fortress after eating something.
Why did he go back to Qinglong Fortress?
You don’t know?
I can't stop him.
Mr. Liu is so stubborn.
He said he couldn’t leave Qinglong Fortress.
He wants to go back and guard.
He really loves my father
to Qinglong Camp.
Yes.
Where's Ni?
Why haven't I seen her?
Poor Ni.
Since we saved her,
she doesn't eat or drink.
Wen Pei forced her
to feed her some water.
No way.
I'm worried that Ni has a heart disease.
So many things happened suddenly.
She's too young to accept it.
Take me to see her.
Sister is here.
Sister
It's okay.
We're safe now.
Sister.
I'm sorry.
What are you talking about?
Why are you sorry?
Remember,
no matter what happens,
you're still my sister.
Got it?
Major Tanaka.
We've successfully entered Shanzhou.
I need to ask my superiors
to reward everyone.
Colonel.
Mr. Tanihara, long time no see.
Thank you.
It's our duty to serve the empire.
It's all thanks to you
you deserve all the credit.
Since you killed
Shangguan Bao died in your hands,
the rest of the bandits have no leader.
and can't get any better.
Colonel.
We can't let our guard down yet.
Our enemy Communist Party
hasn't given up on drawing on swordsmen.
So next,
we must destroy
one by one.
Mr. Tanihara.
This is about the Imperial Army.
What about you?
Have you found the treasure map?
Now I have two maps.
I still need the third one.
This picture is very important.
It is the key to unlock the secret.
We're here
to cooperate with you.
Time is limited and the task is heavy.
The army line of the empire is too long.
The military supply is tight.
If we want to go west as planned,
the supplies must be solved.
Don't worry, Colonel.
I will do my best.
Now that the devil has occupied the city,
Half of the poles on the 18 hills fell.
Some of them fled to the devil.
Those who don't want to surrender
hiding everywhere.
What's going on?
Aren't you usually good at talking?
Why are you so quiet now?
Tell us what you think.
Let me say it.
When the kid is happy,
let’s blow up
like last time?
Or we’ll destroy his command center.
The enemy's current garrison
at least one team.
We can't
with our strength.
I'll go to the main unit.
Only by working with them
to get back where the demons occupy.
I agree with Choi Mun-bae.
That's fine.
How about this?
I'll go with Wen Pei.
You'll pass through many enemy occupations along the way.
I can protect you.
Okay.
We can take care of each other.
No way.
Vegetable buns.
You can go wherever you want.
She... No.
Brother, stop it.
I've made up my mind.
What's your decision?
You decide to stay here?
Let me tell you.
No one can take away
No one can take her away from me.
Vegetable buns.
If you can still breathe,
help me persuade her.
You know her personality.
When she gets stubborn,
I have no choice.
Say it.
I only have one sister.
Wen Kui.
You know her better than I do.
Okay.
Bao.
Let alone our childhood friendship,
Aren't you Communist Party people
Revolutionary friendship?
I've never begged anyone.
I'm begging you today.
Listen carefully.
I'll leave my sister to you today.
As you know,
she is the only family
in this world.
If she loses a hair,
I'll kill you.
Where are you going?
Are you going to see Jang Gong-yeon again?
He's no better than me now.
He's my superior.
I'm his soldier.
I have my team to lead.
You know
what kind of person Jang Gong-yeon is.
Stay.
Fight the devil with us.
Open your eyes and see.
The thirtieth military base.
Are you fighting with bandits?
Choi Moon-Kui, what are you talking about?
Say that again.
Niece, don't be angry.
Brigade Commander Cui is right.
This is a den of bandits.
We're not bandits. What are we?
Brigade Commander Cui is a national army.
Brigadier Cui.
Let's go our separate ways.
Make yourself at home.
We have different paths.
Brigade Commander Cui.
Go ahead.
Don't come with me.
Remember what I said.
Take care of yourself.
I'm leaving.
Wait for my news.
Brother Xi.
Take care of Wen Pei along the way.
Buns
Why is the army like this?
This...
Something's up.
Guys, be alert.
Mr. He. Mr. He.
The Japanese are here.
They surrounded our gate.
Why are you panicking?
Take a look.
Are you surrendering to me?
Mr. He, isn’t this the shop manager?
It turns out to be a devil.
Don't be afraid.
I'll go take a look.
Major Tanaka.
Can I have a word with you?
I can surrender.
But you have to promise me one thing.
Another condition?
When can you cooperate with me
cooperate with me?
I know.
I've already lost everything in front of you.
Now my daughter and Eagle
are in your hands.
But if you don’t agree this time,
I’ll quit.
You can find whoever you want.
Are you threatening me?
Tell me.
My men here have different ideas.
Maybe they have their own ideas.
So please have mercy.
Those who want to join me will stay.
If you don't want to,
please don't make things difficult for them.
Let them go.
Anything else?
I have fulfilled my promise.
and joined the royal army with Qinglong Fortress.
Shouldn't you
let my daughter and Eagle go?
They are living well in the city.
Don't worry about that.
As for those who refuse to surrender,
I promise you.
I can let them go.
Zheng Xiong Tian Yuan.
You've got Qinglong Fortress.
Why won't you let us go?
Am I not clear enough?
Mr. He, what did the devil say?
He said
if we don't surrender,
he will blow up the fortress
and turned Qinglong Fortress into ruins.
Mr. He, what did you say?
I agreed.
What do you mean?
Let's surrender to the devil.
No way.
Who wants to surrender?
Neither do I.
But there are
in the village?
If Master Shangguan
never surrender.
I won't surrender. Fine.
You'll be a cannon fodder for the devil.
We want to live.
I have a family.
Enough.
That devil said
if you don't want to stay,
we can leave the fortress.
How about this?
Go back and tell our brothers.
If you want to stay, stay.
If you really don't want to stay,
ask them to go to the accountant to collect the toll.
Tell them to be careful on the way.
Guards!
Actor table.
Zhang Wen.
and actors.
Su Tianhui, Yang Wanlin, Zhao Dongliang, Chen Yile, Wang Lusheng.
Yue, Wang, Yang Ziyi, Tian Chenzhe, Deng Kai. Mei Liang Dong.
Li, Yu Hongda, Tian Guofeng, Gong, Fan. Cheng Kaiyan.
Sun Zhaoqi, Li Shengchung, Yang Haoyu, and Kkokcho.
to perform.
Zhang Hongbo, Gong Jianfeng, Li Kaiwu, Zhuang, Tao, Sun Haochun.
Zhang Hongbo, Gong Jianfeng, Li Kaiwu, Zhuang, Tao Sun Hao.
Wang Jinjun Liu Jiawen.
Ji, Chao, Zhao Zhigang, Kung, Ji Youyi. Peng Zhenfu.
Xu Fu and Wu Jianyu Zhang Guangyan Sun Yuanwen Chang Qing.
Wu Jinxing, Feng Yonghao, Wei Long, Deng Bao Quan.
Qin HaoSen, Liu Mingjun, Zhang Lianglin.
The legendary army, Liu Hongguo, Yang Chenglin, Liu Yinlong.
Li Zhendong, Chi, Rui, Zhang Ke'er, Yang Junjie. Cui Yuseok.
Zhao Jianhao, Li Xiaoyan, Dong Yuanqi, Sun Tao.
Staff Form.
Director team.
The production team.
Feng Xiaogang.
Photography team.
Ding Weihao.
Lighting Team.
Tian Shuizhou.
The clothing team.
Shi Jangyeong.
The dressing team.
Gong Hae Yeong.
Arts Team.
Props team.
Set team.
Yang Longfei.
Action team.
Fireworks.
The gun team.
Sun Hai.
The recording team.
Wang Wenbo.
The venue team.
Driver team.
Wei Zidian, Qiao Chunsheng, Yang, Tao, Chen Jianfen Kang Jiping.
Li Zhenmin, Dou Xingbin, Wei Ran Jia, Zong Changshun Rong Xi.
Wei Zidian, Qiao Chunsheng, Yang, Tao, Chen Jianfen Jiang Jiping.
Wang Bao Cheung, Su Gao Feng, Liu Deyu, Zhai Yongming. Zou Youwei.
Zhang Chenggui, Su Mingxin, Liu Hongxing, Di Yuping Xu Guanglle.
Xu Ian, Zhang Shou Qiang, Yang Yijiang
Teng Tie Yan, Xu Ian, Zhang Shou Qiang, Yang Yijiang
Ge Wenlong, Song Yongqiang, Wang Daxiong, Yang Ziguang Zhang Jian Ping.
Cut.
Late production.
ZMCG.
Beijing Zhuma Chenguang Culture Co., Ltd.
dubber,
Zhou Xiangning.
Music Producer.
Theme song, Hero.
composed.
Singing Weining Peak Qin Yidan
Thank you, Mr. Wang Xiao, for the title of this drama.
Thank you.
Shandong Blumund Red Film Club. [National 4A Scene Area]
Henan Juntong Car Co., Ltd.
Jintang Jun Kin.
The Public Government of Shanzhou District
The People's Government of Xizhang Village, Shanzhou District
Shanzhou District, Temple, Village Cave Scene.
[Seobu Village Committee of Lingbao City]
Original store is forked.
Zhou Jiajun's kiln in the city.
The village committee of Zhen Kui Village.
The legal consultant service unit.
Henan Lu Da Law Firm.
Special cooperation unit.
There are three Municipal Committee in total.
The People's Government
There are three branches in total.
There are three marketing departments in total.
The Commission of Shanzhou
The People's Government of Shanzhou District
Zhongtong Municipal County Commission.
Henan Henan Yunyang Liquor Co., Ltd.
The People's Government of Laji County.
Henan Henan Boutique Co., Ltd.
The Cultural Responsibility Co., Ltd.
[Sanmen Lanhu City Wetland Park]
Sanmen Cultural Tourism Investment Group.
Yang Tingxuan.
The guidance unit.
Learning to strengthen our country.
The circulation unit.
Qijin (Xiamen) Cultural Media Co., Ltd.
Control unit.
Henan Sandao Movie Development Co., Ltd.
[Joint Film Co., Ltd.]
[Joint filming unit]
The PR Department of Gansu Provincial Committee
Henan Provincial Radio Station.
[Henan Provincial Literature and Arts Association]
TV station.
Henan Provincial Film Association.
Henan Film and TV Group Co., Ltd.
Beijing Times, Yishi Cultural Technology Co., Ltd.
Gansu Lanyi Culture Co., Ltd.
Hebei Army Cultural Media Co., Ltd.
Product unit.
Henan Elephant Film Production Co., Ltd.
Henan Movie Development Co., Ltd.
Qijin (Quan Zhou) Cultural Media Co., Ltd.
Zhang Bing will be rewarded first.